Professional and personal papers of Edwin Wolf 2nd LCP.EW2
Library Company of Philadelphia
- III. Scholarship, Bulk, 1945-1988; 1833-1996
  - IIIb. Research, Bulk, 1945-1988; 1833-1996
    - Charles Ryskamp, "Literary Association Books, 1800-1950," The Princeton University Library Chronicle, 1977, circa 1977 (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Marcus A. McCorison, "Book Trade Labels at the American Antiquarian Society," American Antiquarian Society, 1973, circa 1973 (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Roger E. Stoddard, "Notes on American Play Publishing, 1765-1865," American Antiquarian Society, 1971, circa 1971 (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - Tribute to Clarence Saunders Brigham, 1877-1963, Proceedings of the American Antiquarian Society, 1963, circa 1963 (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - Whitfield J. Bell, Jr., "Archives and Autographs in the American Philosophical Society Library," Proceedings of the American Philosophical Society, 1959, circa 1959 (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - Whitfield J. Bell, Jr., "Astronomical Observatories of the American Philosophical Society, 1769-1843," Proceedings of the American Philosophical Society, 1964, circa 1964 (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - Whitfield J. Bell, Jr., "As Others Saw Us: Notes on the Reputation of the American Philosophical Society," Proceedings of the American Philosophical Society, 1972, circa 1972 (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - Whitfield J. Bell, Jr., "I. Minis Hays, Secretary, Librarian, and Benefactor of the American Philosophical Society," Proceedings of the American Philosophical Society, 1975, circa 1975 (Box 34, Folder 38)
    - George F. Kennan and Whitfield J. Bell, Jr., "Views from Another East Berlin," Proceedings of the American Philosophical Society, 1982, circa 1982 (Box 34, Folder 39)
    - William Roach, "Francisque Michel: A Pioneer in Medieval Studies," Proceedings of the American Philosophical Society, 1970, circa 1970 (Box 34, Folder 40)
    - Kenneth M. Setton, "The Byzantine Background to the Italian Renaissance," Proceedings of the American Philosophical Society, 1956, circa 1956 (Box 34, Folder 41)
    - Bernard Bailyn, "Morison: An Appreciation," Proceedings of the Massachusetts Historical Society, 1977, circa 1977 (Box 34, Folder 42)
    - "Lyman Henry Butterfield: Commemorations of His Life by Marc Friedlaender, Olive G. Malcolm, Whitfield J. Bell, Jr., and Fox Butterfield," Proceedings of the Massachusetts Historical Society, 1982, circa 1982 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - John Freehafer, " Cardenio, by Shakespeare and Fletcher," Publications of the Modern Language Association of America, 1969, circa 1969 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - J. A. Leo Lemay, "Richard Lewis and Augustan American Poetry, " Publications of the Modern Language Association of America, 1968, circa 1968 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - David M. Vieth, "Poems by 'My Lord R.': Rochester versus Radclyffe," Publications of the Modern Language Association of America, 1957, circa 1957 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - H. Trevor Colbourn, "The Reading of Joseph Carrington Cabell: 'A List of Books on Various Subjects Recommended to a Young Man...'," Studies in Bibliography, 1960, circa 1960 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - C. William Miller, "Thomas Newcomb: A Restoration Printer's Ornament Stock," Studies in Bibliography, 1950-1951, circa 1951 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - C. William Miller, "A London Ornament Stock: 1598-1683," Studies in Bibliography, 1955, circa 1955 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - G. Thomas Tanselle, "A System of Color Identification for Bibliographical Description," Studies in Bibliography, 1967, circa 1967 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - G. Thomas Tanselle, "The Bibliographical Description of Patterns," Studies in Bibliography, 1970, circa 1970 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Ted-Larry Pebworth, "Bibliographical Notes: New Light on Sir Henry Wotton's 'The Character of a Happy Life'," The Transactions of the Bibliographical Society: The Library, 1978, circa 1978 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Norman S. Fiering, "President Samuel Johnson and the Circle of Knowledge," The William and Mary Quarterly, 1971, circa 1971 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Norman S. Fiering, "The Transatlantic Republic of Letters: A Note on the Circulation of Learned Periodicals to Early Eighteenth-Century America," The William and Mary Quarterly, 1976, circa 1976 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Caroline Robbins, "Absolute Liberty: The Life and Thought of William Popple, 1638-1708," The William and Mary Quarterly, 1967, circa 1967 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Justin G. Turner, "Manuscripts and History," address delivered at the Annual Meeting of the American Association for State and Local History at Houston, Texas, October 24, 1952, circa 1952 (Box 35, Folder 14)
- IV. Photographs by Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1970s
  - Photographic prints: Self portraits, 1970s (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Photographic prints: Portraits and candid shots of various people, 1970s (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Photographic prints: Portraits and candid shots of various people, 1970s (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Photographic prints: Landscapes and various objects, 1970s (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Photographic prints: Landscapes and various objects, 1970s (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Contact sheets, 1970s (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Photographic negatives, 1970s (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Photographic negatives, 1970s (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Photographic prints, negatives, slide, and notes from photography class, 1970s (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Titled and matted photographic prints, 1970s (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - "Philadelphia's Coming of Age, 1745-1785" Winterthur slide album, 1970s (Box 36, Folder 6)